Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- 10th Anniversary Excerpts Rebroadcast: Tony Kushner Play, Ruth Knafo Setton, Roya Hakakian, Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Judith Malena Reads Grace Paley, Music by Sarah Aroeste, Basya Schechter, Lorin Sklamberg, Lisa Gutkins, Alex Kontorovich, Abe Velez, 2008-07-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_224)
- Gerard Edery, 1 Hour Fundraiser, 2008-07-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_225)
- Krakow's Jewish Cultural Festival, 2008-08-10 (Box Electronic Records, Case TW_TAM_718_ER_193)
- Jeremy Ben-Ami of J Street; Krakow Jewish Cultural Festival Coverage by Alisa Solomon and Marilyn K. Neimark; Obituaries for Mahmoud Darwish and Adina Back, 2008-08-10 (Box 19, Item 718_0831)
- Jeremy Ben-Ami of J Street, 2008-08-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_196)
- Jeremy Ben-Ami of J Street; Krakow Jewish Cultural Festival; Remembering Mahmoud Darwish, 2008-08-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_226)
- Krakow Jewish Cultural Festival Summer 2008 with Alisa Solomon and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, 2008-08-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_265)
- Marcel Khalife Reading "My Mother" by Mahmoud Darwish, 2008-08-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_270)
- Aircheck, 2008-08-17 (Box 19, Item 718_0833)
- Vasily Grossman Rebroadcast, 2008-08-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_227)
- Antony Beevor (Unedited), 2008-08-17 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_271)
- Thomas Powers on Iran; Anshel Pfeffer on Georgia and Israel; Martha Schwendener on Action/Abstraction Exhibition, 2008-08-24 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_229)
- Jeff Halper of Free Gaza Movement; Joel Campagna of Committee to Protect Journalists; Sylvia Barack Fishman on Brandeis University Gender Study, 2008-08-31 (Box 19, Item 718_0832)
- Jeff Halper of Free Gaza Movement; Sylvia Fishman on Brandeis University Gender Study, 2008-08-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_194)
- Joe Compagna of Committee to Protect Journalists, 2008-08-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_195)
- Jeff Halper, Sylvia Fishman, and Joel Campagna, 2008-08-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_228)
- Ari Berman, Nathaniel Popper, and Udi Aloni, 2008-09-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_230)
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Part 2, 2008-09-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_231)
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Part 2, 2008-09-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_232)
- Nomi Prins on Financial Crisis and Bailout; Gabriel Kahane on His New Album; Mik Moore with Esther Kaplan on "The Great Schlep" Voting Campaign, 2008-10-05 (Box 20, Item 718_0863)
- Mik Moore with Esther Kaplan on "The Great Schlep" Voting Campaign, 2008-10-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_199)
- Nomi Prins on Financial Crisis and Bailout; Gabriel Kahane on His New Album; Mik Moore with Esther Kaplan on "The Great Schlep" Voting Campaign, 2008-10-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_233)
- Ami Eden on Jewish Voters; Sarah Ludwig on Effects of Financial Crisis on Homeowners, 2008-10-12 (Box 20, Item 718_0862)
- Ami Eden on Jewish Voters; Sarah Ludwig on Effects of Financial Crisis on Homeowners, 2008-10-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_234)
- Zoher Bahalul on Riots in Akko; Paul Shapiro on Essen; Myrna Perez on Voter Purges, 2008-10-19 (Box 19, Item 718_0860)
- Yaacob Dweck on Khirbet Khizeh, 2008-10-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_197)
- Zoher Bahalul on Riots in Akko; Paul Shapiro on Essen; Myrna Perez on Voter Purges, 2008-10-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_235)
- Yaacob Dweck on Khirbet Khizeh, 2008-10-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_204)
- Chip Berlet on the Financial Meltdown and Anti-Semitism; Robert Meeropol Interview; Yaacob Dweck on Khirbet Khizeh, 2008-10-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_236)
- Robert Meeropol (Unedited), 2008-10-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_264)
- State Senator Eric Schneiderman on New York Senate Races; Laila al-Qahtani on New FBI Guidelines; Jeremy Gillick on "Chabad in the West Bank"; Oded Efrati on Assisting the Olive Harvest, 2008-11-02 (Box 19, Item 718_0844)
- Eric Schneiderman on State Senate Races; Laila al-Qahtani on New FBI Guidelines; Jeremy Gillick on Chabad on the West Bank; Oded Efrat on Israelis who Pick Olives for Palestinians, 2008-11-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_237)
- Manning Marable and Bob Moser on Obama Victory; Paul Reale on Climate Change Activism, 2008-11-09 (Box 19, Item 718_0843)
- Election with Manning Marable and Bob Moser; Climate Change with Paul Reale, 2008-11-09 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_238)
- Mikey Weinstein, 2008-11-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_200)
- Marshall T. Meyer Risk-Taker Award Recipients Maria Muentes and Mikey Weinstein; Steven Blier on NY Festival of Song's Fugitives Concert, 2008-11-16 (Box 19, Item 718_0845)
- Marshall T. Meyer Risk Taker Award Recipients Maria Muentes and Mikey Weinstein; Steven Blier on New York Festival of Songs Fugitives Concert, 2008-11-16 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_239)
- Nathaniel Popper on Postville, Iowa; Neve Gordon on Israel's Occupation; Richard Kim on Prop 8, 2008-11-23 (Box 19, Item 718_0847)
- Nathaniel Popper on Agriprocessors and Postville, Iowa; Neve Gordon, Israel's Occupation; Richard Kim on Proposition 8, 2008-11-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_240)
- Andre Schiffrin on Studs Terkel; Studs Terkel Interviews from Hard Times; Alisa Solomon Interviews Susan Tumarkin Goodman on Chagall and the Artists of the Russian Jewish Theater Exhibition, 2008-11-30 (Box 19, Item 718_0840)
- Andre Schiffrin on Studs Terkel; Interviews Conducted by Studs Terkel for Hard Times; Alisa Solomon Interviews Susan Tumarkin Goodman on Jewish Museum Exhibition Chagall and the Artists of the Russian Jewish Theater, 1919-1949, 2008-11-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_241)
- Studs Terkel Interviews for Hard Times: Mary Owsley, Horace Cayton, and Virginia Durr, 2008-11-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_268)
- Aram Roston on Mumbai; Obama Foreign Policy Appointments with Phyllis Bennis; John D'Emilio on Milk, 2008-12-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_242)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Susan Tumarkin Godman on Chagall and the Artists of the Russian Jewish Theater, 191-1949 Exhibition at the Jewish Museum, 2008-12-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_266)
- Aram Roston on Mumbai Violence; Phyllis Bennis on Obama Foreign Policy Appointments; John D'Emilio on Milk, 2008-12-07 (Box 19, Item 718_0842)
- 12/8/2008 Demonstration, 2008-12-08 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_202)
- Jenny Romaine and Joe Dobkin Reading Works from the Great Depression by Clifford Odets, S.J. Perelman, Tess Slesinger, Anzia Yezierska, and Mike Gold, 2008-12-14 (Box 19, Item 718_0846)
- Woody Guthrie: Hobo's Lullaby, Worried Man Blues, Hard Times, 2008-12-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_198)
- Aircheck 2 (Partial), 2008-12-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_244)
- Waiting for Santa, Jobs in the Sky, The Day Santa Claus Fainted, 2008-12-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_267)
- Depression Readings: Waiting for Lefty (Odets), Waiting for Santy (S.J. Perelman), Red Ribbon on a White Horse (from The New Poor by Anzia Yezierska), 2008-12-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_273)
- Geraldine Brooks, 2008-12-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_209)
- Lubna Masarwa on Student Trip; Melissa Berman on Bernie Madoff; Kiera Feldman on JFREJ Children's Vigil, 2008-12-21 (Box 19, Item 718_0834)
- Lubna Masarwa of the Free Gaza Movement; Melissa Berman on Bernard Madoff; Children's Vigil, December 8, 2008, JFREJ and Domestic Workers United, 2008-12-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_245)
- Gaza Demonstration; Tel Aviv 12/27/2008 Airstrikes; 1/3/2009 Invasion; 1/18/2009 Unilateral Ceasefire; 1/21/2009 Withdrawal Completed; 1400 Palestinians and 13 Israelis Killed, 2008 December 27 - 2009 January 21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_299)
- Chris Hayes on Rahm Emanuel; Frank Mauro on New York State Budget; Michel Warschawski on Israel Attack on Gaza, 2008-12-28 (Box 19, Item 718_0830)
- Chris Hayes on Rahm Emanuel (Partial); Frank Mauro on New York State Budget; Readings from Ewa Jasiewicz on Gaza Attacks; Michel Warschawski on Israeli Attack on Gaza, 2008-12-28 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_246)
- Israeli Settlement Freeze; Goldstone Report Reactions [2015-008], 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_584)
- Yiddish Radio and Joe Amar, circa 2009 (Box 11, Item 718_0382)
- Tel Aviv Protest Against Gaza Attacks; Fuel for Truth Report; Josh King on And You Shall Know Us By the Trail of Our Vinyl, 2009-01-04 (Box 20, Item 718_0893)
- Netivot by Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark and Alisa Solomon; Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark from Tel Aviv; Donna Nevel on Gaza Protest of January 12; Alan Lavine Interviews Thomas Sugrue on Sweet Land of Liberty: the Forgotten Struggle for Civil Rights in the North; Nan Rubin Remembers Helen Suzman, 2009-01-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_306)
- Dalit Baum on "Who Profits?" Database; Juan Mandelbaum and David Heilbroner Discussion of New York Jewish Film Festival and Their Films Waiting for Armageddon and Our Disappeared, 2009-01-18 (Box 20, Item 718_0898)
- Sarah Posner on Rev. Rick Warren's Inaugural Invocation; Shevy Korzen on Hotline for Migrant Workers in Israel; Jane Eisner on The Forward, 2009-01-25 (Box 20, Item 718_0881)
- Sarah Posner on Rev. Rick Warren; Shevy Korzen on Hotline for Migrant Workers in Israel; Jane Eisner of The Forward, 2009-01-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_304)
- Shevy Korzen on Hotline for Migrant Workers in Israel, 2009-01-25 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_293)
- Avraham (Avram) Burg, The Holocaust Is Over, We Must Rise From its Ashes, 2009-01-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_281)
- American Israel Public Affairs Committee (AIPAC) Northeast Regional Dinner with Josh Nathan-Kazis and Kiera Feldman, 2009-02-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_291)
- AIPAC Northeast Regional Dinner and Protest; Gentrification and the Weitzman School in Jaffa, Israel; Danish Jewish Museum in Copenhagen, 2009-02-01 (Box 20, Item 718_0874)
- Orna Baranes on Weitzman School in Jaffa, 2009-02-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_292)
- AIPAC Dinner Report by Josh Nathan-Kazis and Kiera Feldman; Housing in Jaffa; Weitzman School in Jaffa; Danish Jewish Museum Report by Mark Laiosa, 2009-02-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_311)
- Jaffa Housing, 2009-02-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_362)
- Ayman Mohyeldin on Israeli Assault on Gaza; Matan Cohen on Divestment from Companies Involved with Israeli Occupation; Dave Zirin on Impact of Israeli-Palestinian Conflict on Sports; Michel Warschawski on Israeli Elections, Part 1, 2009-02-15 (Box 20, Item 718_0864)
- Excerpts from Our City Dreams; Interview with Nancy Spero, Part 2, 2009-02-15 (Box 20, Item 718_0873)
- Marathon: Ayman Mohyeldin, Marfan Cohen, David Ziren, and Michel Warschawski, Part 1, 2009-02-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_312)
- Marathon: Nancy Spero, Part 2, 2009-02-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_314)
- Nancy Spero, 2009-02-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_361)
- Brian Byrnes on Holocaust-Denying Bishop; Liel Leibovitz on Waltz with Bashir; Abe Velez Interview with Gustavo Bulgach of Klezmer Juice, 2009-03-01 (Box 20, Item 718_0872)
- Brian Byrnes on Bishop Williamson's Expulsion from Argentina; Liel Leibovitz on Waltz with Bashir; Klezmer Juice with Abe Velez, 2009-03-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_313)
- Esther Kaplan Interviews Brian Byrnes in Argentina about Bishop Williamson, 2009-03-01 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_356)
- Philip Weiss on Scuttling of Chas Freeman Nomination; Daniel Levy on New Likud Government; Keith Gessen on His Essay "People of the Book", 2009-03-15 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_315)
- Josh Nathan-Kazis on Lawfare Conference, 2009-03-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_283)
- San Francisco Rally for Tristan Anderson; Reading of Seven Jewish Children by Caryl Churchill with Kathleen Chalfant, Brian Jones, Daren Kelly, Una Aya Osato, and Brian Pickett; Liz Alpern on Small Southern Colleges Recruiting Jewish Students (Partial), 2009-03-22 (Box 20, Item 718_0876)
- Tristan Anderson Rally in San Francisco (Partial); Seven Jewish Children: A Play for Gaza by Caryl Churchill with Kathleen Chalfant, Brian Pickett, Brian Jones, and Una Aya Osato; Elizabeth Alpern on Jewish Students Being Recruited by Small Southern Colleges, 2009-03-22 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_316)
- Tristan Anderson Rally in San Francisco, 2009-03-22 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_351)
- Eyal Weizman on "Lawfare in Gaza: Legislative Attack" Essay; Kiera Feldman on Birthright Israel; Leslie Cagan on United for Peace and Justice's (UFPJ)'s April 4th Action on Wall Street, 2009-03-29 (Box 20, Item 718_0885)
- Birthright Israel, 2009-03-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_308)
- Eyal Weizman Regarding Essay on "Lawfare in Gaza"; Kiera Feldman on Birthright Israel; Leslie Cagan on April 4 Wall Street Demonstration (Partial), 2009-03-29 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_317)
- Tel Aviv Anti-war Protests with Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark and Alisa Solomon; Fuel for Truth with Josh Nathan-Kazis and Kiera Feldman; Josh Kun with Roger Bennett on And You Shall Know Us by the Trail of Our Vinyl: The Jewish Past as Told by the Records We Have Loved, 2009-04-04 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_303)
- Dalia Kandiyoti Talks with Jonathan Freedman about His Book Klezmer America: Jewishness, Ethnicity, Modernity, 2009-04-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_205)
- Senator Liz Krueger on New York State Budget; Rabbi Arthur Waskow on 40th Anniversary of the Freedom Seder and the Blessing of the Sun, 2009-04-05 (Box 20, Item 718_0882)
- Dalia Kandiyoti Interviews Jonathan Feldman on Klezmer America, 2009-04-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_305)
- Senator Liz Krueger on New York State Budget; Rabbi Arthur Waskow on 40th Anniversary of the Freedom Seder and the Blessing of the Sun; Dalia Kandiyoti with Jonathan Freedman about His Book, Klezmer America, 2009-04-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_318)
- Abe Velez Music Show with Jeremiah Lockwood and Balkan Beat Box; Josh Nathan-Kazis on Aharit Hayamim, 2009-04-12 (Box 20, Item 718_0886)
- Abe Velez Hosts All Music Show with the Swan Machinery's Jeremiah Lockwood; Josh Nathan-Kazis Report on Acharit Hayamim, 2009-04-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_319)
- Acharit Hayamim, 2009-04-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_359)
- Richard Falk on Israel/Gaza Human Rights Violations; Assemblymember Linda Rosenthal and Alissa Wise on Domestic Workers Rights; Eran Riklis on Lemon Tree, 2009-04-19 (Box 20, Item 718_0884)
- Richard Falk on Calls to Investigate Israel for War Crimes in Gaza; Linda Rosenthal on Domestic Workers Bill of Rights; Eran Riklis on His Film Lemon Tree, 2009-04-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_322)
- Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz Interviews Eran Riklis, Director of The Lemon Tree, 2009-04-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_355)
- Philip Weiss on Rep. Jane Harman Transcripts; WBAI Benefit Screening of Encounter Point; Cecilie Surasky on U.N.'s Durban Review Conference in Geneva, 2009-04-26 (Box 20, Item 718_0870)
- Philip Weiss on Rep. Jane Harman Transcripts; WBAI Benefit Screening of Encounter Point; Cecilie Surasky on U.N.'s Durban Review Conference in Geneva, 2009-04-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_320)
- Encounter Point Rebroadcast, 2009-04-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_354)
- Diana Dolev on Israeli Government Raid; Michael Ratner on Torture Memos and Obama Response; Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark and Esther Kaplan on Senator Arlen Specter Defection; Part One of Steve Zeitlin Talk on Jewish Humor, 2009-05-03 (Box 20, Item 718_0880)
- Diana Dolev on Israeli Government Raids on 4/26 and Violent Police Response at 4/30 Demonstration; Michael Ratner on Torture Memos and Obama Responses; Esther Kaplan and Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark on Senator Arlen Specter Defection; Part 1 of Steve Zeitlin Talk on Jewish Humor, 2009-05-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_321)
- Michael Ratner Torture Memos, 2009-05-03 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_297)
- Music Special Hosted by Abe Velez with Basya Schechter, Roberto Rodriguez, and Sarah Aroeste, 2009-05-10 (Box 20, Item 718_0871)
- Marathon Music Special: Abe Velez with Basya Schechter on Her Band, Part 1, 2009-05-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_323)
- Marathon Music Special: Abe Velez with Roberto Rodriguez and Sarah Aroeste, Part 2, 2009-05-10 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_324)
- Sarah Ludwig on Credit Card Reform Legislation; Abe Velez on Hip Hop Hoodio's New CD, Carne Masada; Jeff Sharlet on Fundamentalists in Military, 2009-05-31 (Box 20, Item 718_0888)
- Sarah Ludwig on Credit Card Reform Legislation; Abe Velez and Josh Norek on Carne Masada; Jeff Sharlet on His Article, "Jesus Killed Mohammed," and Fundamentalists in the Military, 2009-05-31 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_325)
- Kiera Feldman with Felice Gelman on Gaza Delegation; Dan Fleshler on Transforming America's Israel Lobby; Jeremy Gillick on Article, "The Coming of the Intermarried Rabbi", 2009-06-07 (Box 20, Item 718_0889)
- Kiera Feldman with Felice Gelman on Gaza Delegation; Dan Fleshler on Transforming America's Israel Lobby; Jeremy Gillick on Article, "The Coming of the Intermarried Rabbi", 2009-06-07 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_327)
- Abe Velez with Frank London, 2009-06-14 (Box 20, Item 718_0892)
- Abe Velez with Frank London, 2009-06-14 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_328)
- Nathaniel Popper on Congress Hotel Strike in Chicago; Leonard Zeskind on Book,Blood and Politics and White Supremacy; Naftaly Gliksberg on Look Into My Eyes, 2009-06-21 (Box 20, Item 718_0867)
- Nathaniel Popper on Congress Hotel Strike in Chicago; Leonard Zeskind on White Supremacy and His Book, Blood and Politics; Naftaly Gliksberg on Look Into My Eyes, 2009-06-21 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_329)
- Gay Pride: Alisa Solomon with Haneen Maikey, Richard Kim, and Tim McCaskell, 2009-06-28 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_296)
- Tom Robbins on State Senate Meltdown; Roya Hakakian on Iranian Elections; Ewa Jasiewicz on Boat Interdiction, 2009-07-05 (Box 20, Item 718_0875)
- Tom Robbins State Senate - What's at Stake?; Roya Hakakian on Iran; Ewa Jasiewicz of Free Gaza Movement, 2009-07-05 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_331)
- Max Fraser Interviews Beryl Satter on Family Properties: Race, Real Estate, and the Exploitation of Black Urban America, 2009-07-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_353)
- Rep. Jerrold Nadler on Health Care Reform; Geoffrey Aronson on Diplomatic Efforts to Freeze Settlements; Aviva Kempner, Director of Yoo-Hoo, Mrs. Goldberg, 2009-07-12 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_330)
- Alisa Solomon with Yael Bartana on Exhibition; Lev Dodin on Life and Fate; Mark Laiosa with Lev Raphael on My Germany, 2009-07-19 (Box 20, Item 718_0895)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Yael Bartana, 2009-07-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_298)
- Alisa Solomon Interviews Israeli Artist Yael Bartana; Lev Dodin on Life and Fate at Lincoln Center Festival; Mark Laiosa interviews Lev Raphael on My Germany, 2009-07-19 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_332)
- Alisa Solomon, Haneen Maikey, and Richard Kim on Israel's Branding Campaign Targeting LGBTQ Communities; Beryl Satter on Book Family Properties, 2009-07-26 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_333)
- Adina Hoffman on My Happiness Bears No Relation to Happiness: A Poet's Life in the Palestinian Century, 2009-08-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_310)
- Taha Muhammad Ali with Peter Cole, Readings: "Revenge" and "Abd el-Hadi Fights a Superpower", 2009-08-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_357)
- Taha Muhammad Ali with Peter Cole, Readings, 2009-08-02 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_358)
- Rachel Tzvia Back on With an Iron Pen: Twenty Years of Hebrew Protest Poetry, 2009-08-11 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_335)
- Mazel Tov Mis Amigos with Abe Velez, 2009-08-23 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_336)
- Neve Gordon on Israel Boycott; Daniel Levy about the Israel Project; Esther Broner on The Red Squad, 2009-08-30 (Box 20, Item 718_0877)
- Josh Nathan-Kazis with Daniel Levy on The Israel Project, 2009-08-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_279)
- Esther Broner on The Red Squad, 2009-08-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_280)
- Neve Gordon on BDS Movement; Josh Nathan-Kazis Talks with Daniel Leux about The Israel Project; Esther Broner on Her Book The Red Squad, 2009-08-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_337)
- Esther Broner on Her Book The Red Squad, 2009-08-30 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_352)
- Kiera Feldman Reports on Jews for Jesus Campaign, 2009-09-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_302)
- Timothy Snyder on Holocaust: The Ignored Reality; Mandy Katz on Branding Israel; Jews for Jesus, 36th Annual Summer Witnessing Campaign, 2009-09-06 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_339)
- Abe Velez Music, 2009-09-13 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_338)
- Co-host Kiera Feldman with Rabbi Arthur Waskow on Conference of Presidents and Goldstone Gaza Report; Mandy Katz on Israel's Branding Campaign; Judith Belasco on Jewish Food Movement, 2009-09-20 (Box 20, Item 718_0866)
- Judith Belasco on Jewish Food Movement, 2009-09-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_282)
- Rabbi Arthur Waskow, 2009-09-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_301)
- Arthur Waskow on Iran; Goldstone Gaza Report; Mandy Katz on Israel Branding; Judith Belasco on Jewish Food Movement, 2009-09-20 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_340)
- Emily Seif Reporting on Westboro Baptist Church, 2009-09-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_284)
- A Report from Westboro Baptist Church Protests at Brooklyn Synagogues; Phyllis Bennis, Rashid Khalidi, and Avi Shlaim on Goldstone Report; Jeffrey Shandler on Jews, God, and Videotape, 2009-09-27 (Box 20, Item 718_0865)
- Alisa Solomon with Jeffrey Shandler, 2009-09-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_300)
- A Report from Westboro Baptist Church Anti-Jew, Anti-Gay Protests at Brooklyn Synagogues; Phyllis Bennis, Rashid Khalidi, and Avi Shlaim on Freeze and Goldstone Report; Alisa Solomon Talks with Jeff Shandler on Khazans, 2009-09-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_341)
- Cantors: Kol Nidre (Rosenblatt, Oysler, Tucker), Avinu Malkeinu (Jennie Goldstein, B. Streisand), 2009-09-27 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_360)